<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Damodor</string>
    <string name="mr_mckenic_first_page">Mr.McKenic Chemicals (Singapore)</string>
    <string name="gk_germkiller_first_page"> GK Germ Killer (Singapore) </string>
    <string name="engineering_first_page">Engineering Services</string>


    //GermKiller product description
    <string name="gk_surface_wipes_description">
        GK Surface™ is a water-based disinfectant that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. This multi-action formula cleans and disinfects surfaces.
        \n
        \nKills up to 99.99999% of bacteria and viruses
        \nFormulated for daily use
        \nEffective against mould and mildew
        \nLeaves an antimicrobial film on surface for up to 30 days
        \n
        \n
        20 wipes per pack
    </string>

    <string name="gk_surface_liquid_description">
        GK Surface™ is a water-based disinfectant that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. This multi-action formula cleans and disinfects surfaces.
        \n
        \nKills up to 99.99999% of bacteria and viruses
        \nFormulated for daily use
        \nEffective against mould and mildew
        \nLeaves an antimicrobial film on surface for up to 30 days
        \n
        \n
        85ml, 500ml, 5L
    </string>

    <string name="gk_air_description">
        GK Air™ is a water-based air disinfectant that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. It improves air quality by destroying odour-causing bacteria, instead of masking the bad odour with fragrance. Suitable for daily indoor use.
        \n
        \nFreshens air in indoor environments
        \nSafe for daily indoor use
        \nNon-flammable
        \nRefreshing green tea fragrance
        \nDoes not contain propellant
        \nSurfactant free
        \n
        \n
        \n300ml, 5L Bottle
    </string>
    <string name="gk_concentrate_description">
        GK Concentrate™ is a water-based disinfectant concentrate that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. This multipurpose formula cleans, disinfects and protects, leaving a long-lasting and fragrant scent. Suitable for daily use.
        \n
        \nKills up to 99.99999% bacteria and viruses
        \nLight detergent action
        \nWorks against mould and mildew
        \nSanitises laundry
        \nDestroys bad odour at source
        \nSafe for daily use
        \nSafe for daily useSafe for daily use
        \nCertified under “Singapore Green Label”
        \nCertified under “Singapore Green Label”Certified under “Singapore Green Label”

        \nTested effective against SARS-CoV-2 (actual COVID-19 virus).
        \nCertified Hospital-Grade Disinfectant (AOAC efficacy evaluation requirement for hospital grade disinfectants)
        \nSafe for daily use around humans, pets and the environment (Testing of Chemicals for Health Effects as per OECD Guidelines)
        \nTested non-toxic and non-irritating for the skin, eyes, and mouth. Tested against skin sensitisation and irritation (Testing of Chemicals for Health Effects as per OECD Guidelines).
        \n
        \n500ml, 2L , 5L

    </string>

</resources>