<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Damodor</string>
    <string name="mr_mckenic_first_page">Mr.McKenic Chemicals (Singapore)</string>
    <string name="gk_germkiller_first_page"> GK Germ Killer (Singapore) </string>
    <string name="engineering_first_page">Engineering Services</string>


    //GermKiller product description
    <string name="gk_surface_wipes_description">
        GK Surface™ is a water-based disinfectant that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. This multi-action formula cleans and disinfects surfaces.
        \n
        \nKills up to 99.99999% of bacteria and viruses
        \nFormulated for daily use
        \nEffective against mould and mildew
        \nLeaves an antimicrobial film on surface for up to 30 days
        \n
        \n
        20 wipes per pack
    </string>

    <string name="gk_surface_liquid_description">
        GK Surface™ is a water-based disinfectant that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. This multi-action formula cleans and disinfects surfaces.
        \n
        \nKills up to 99.99999% of bacteria and viruses
        \nFormulated for daily use
        \nEffective against mould and mildew
        \nLeaves an antimicrobial film on surface for up to 30 days
        \n
        \n
        85ml, 500ml, 5L
    </string>

    <string name="gk_air_description">
        GK Air™ is a water-based air disinfectant that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. It improves air quality by destroying odour-causing bacteria, instead of masking the bad odour with fragrance. Suitable for daily indoor use.
        \n
        \nFreshens air in indoor environments
        \nSafe for daily indoor use
        \nNon-flammable
        \nRefreshing green tea fragrance
        \nDoes not contain propellant
        \nSurfactant free
        \n
        \n
        \n300ml, 5L Bottle
    </string>
    <string name="gk_concentrate_description">
        GK Concentrate™ is a water-based disinfectant concentrate that effectively eliminates up to 99.99999% of germs. This multipurpose formula cleans, disinfects and protects, leaving a long-lasting and fragrant scent. Suitable for daily use.
        \n
        \nKills up to 99.99999% bacteria and viruses
        \nLight detergent action
        \nWorks against mould and mildew
        \nSanitises laundry
        \nDestroys bad odour at source
        \nSafe for daily use
        \nSafe for daily useSafe for daily use
        \nCertified under “Singapore Green Label”
        \nCertified under “Singapore Green Label”Certified under “Singapore Green Label”

        \nTested effective against SARS-CoV-2 (actual COVID-19 virus).
        \nCertified Hospital-Grade Disinfectant (AOAC efficacy evaluation requirement for hospital grade disinfectants)
        \nSafe for daily use around humans, pets and the environment (Testing of Chemicals for Health Effects as per OECD Guidelines)
        \nTested non-toxic and non-irritating for the skin, eyes, and mouth. Tested against skin sensitisation and irritation (Testing of Chemicals for Health Effects as per OECD Guidelines).
        \n
        \n500ml, 2L , 5L

    </string>






    //Mr.Mckenic Product Description

    <string name="ac1923_description">
        Mr McKenic® – Processed Alkaline Industrial Coil Cleaner is an essential component in the successful cleaning and maintenance of cooling coils.
        \n
        \n Mr McKenic® – Processed Alkaline Industrial Coil Cleaner is easy to apply and highly effective in breaking up grimes, dirt, airborne impurities and scale deposits thereby leaving coils dirt-free and shining. This product is strongly recommended for use in all routine air-con cleaning to increase efficiency and to reduce electrical cost.
        \n
        \n Product Code:Processed Alkaline Industrial Coil
        \n CleanerAvailable
        \n
        \n Available Sizes: 5 Liter ,25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="ac1926_description">
        Conventional methods of cleaning the air conditioner units are generally complicated and tedious and engaging professional services are often costly. The Do-It-Yourself concept from Mr McKenic® – Air-Conditioner Cleaner (Self-Rinsing) offers a simpler and more cost-effective alternative for your regular maintenance routines.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 500ml, 5 Liter ,25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="bc8618_description">
        Mr McKenic® – Cream Polisher is a uniquely formulated product which effectively cleans and polishes different surface types such as stainless steel, metal, aluminum, and tiles.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® – Cream Polisher is non-fuming and non-corrosive, hence it is safe to use on most sensitive surfaces and will not cause discoloration of exterior walls.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 20 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="dr8211_1_description">
        Mr Mckenic 0Multi Purpose cleaner (M97-1) is technically designed to transform water and weak solvents into stronger cleaning and emulsifying solution.
        \n
        \nMr Mckenic – Multipurpose cleaner (m97-1) is widely used in component cleaning, automotives, heavy industries, aviation, marine hotel, school, building, refineries, oil and gas industry, etc.
        \n
        \n Available Sizes: 20 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="ee1325_description">
        \n
        \nMr Mckenic® - Contact Cleaner and Lubricant is a cleaning solvent for removing dust, dirt deposits; etc… from contact points yet lubricates the mechanism. It helps to prevent short-circuit by displacing moisture. At the same time, it leaves a film of protection that protects against oxidation on contact points.
        \n
        \nMr Mckenic® - Contact Cleaner and Lubricant is widely used in electrical parts, switchboard, mechanical parts, electronic equipment, computers, electronics and electrical industries.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 400ml Can
    </string>
    <string name="ee1331_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Contact Cleaner (Fast Dry) is a cleaning solvent for removing dust, dirt deposits, etc from contact points, sensitive surfaces containing circuitry or PCB boards.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Contact Cleaner (Fast Dry) is widely used in electrical parts, switchboards, mechanical parts, electronics equipment, computers, electronic and electrical industries, etc
        \n
        \n Available Sizes: 400ml Can
    </string>
    <string name="ee1332_a_description">
        As part of our constant efforts towards environmental protection, we are pleased to unveil a greener and environmental-friendlier solvent cleaner, Mr McKenic® – EE1332 Contact Cleaner.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® – EE1332 Contact Cleaner is a non-CFC, non-HCFC cleaning solvent for general industrial and maintenance use. It effectively dissolves and removes dust, dirt, grime, grease, tar, adhesives and flux from electrical and electronic contact points.
        \n
        \nIt is quick drying and evaporates without leaving any residue. This product is suitable for use on electronic parts, metal and most plastics.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 422gm
    </string>
    <string name="gg3012_description">
        Mr McKenic – Anti-Seize Compound is formulated as a heavy duty high load and high temperature anti-seize that will not pound out of the bearing of fitting.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic – Anti-Seize is widely used in the industrial machineries, offshore, shipyards, marines, constructions, sewage plants, elevators, paper mills, aircraft industries, food processing plants, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 5Kg Pail

    </string>
    <string name="gg3017_description">
        Mr McKenic - Non-Melt Red Grease is formulated as a heavy duty high load and high temperature grease that will not pound out of the bearing of fitting.
        \n
        \nMr Mckenic- Non -Melt Red Grease widely used in the industrial machineries, offshore, shipyards, marines, constructions, sewage plants, elevators, paper mills aircraft industries, food processing plant, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 5Kg Pail
    </string>
    <string name="gg3020_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Synthetic High Temperature Grease is a synthetic high temperature grease formulated with special selection of graphite and olefin polymer and thickener.
        \n
        \nApplied to all types of shaft, open gears and bearings operating at medium-low speed and high temperatures. It can be applied by any conventional greasing equipment.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 5Kg Pail ,1Kg Pail
    </string>
    <string name="lu1801_description">
        Mr McKenic - Dry Moly Lubricant is formulated to give suspension and long lasting lubrication. It forms a thin black coating with excellent anti friction and anti-seize properties. The coating is able to protect surfaces from moisture, rust and corrosion and it can withstand high temperature and extreme pressure. This product adheres best to metal.
        \n
        \nMr.Mckenic - Dry Moly lubricant is widely used in high speed gears, bearings, slides, assemblies, converyors, tools ,moving parts, joints, hinges, cams, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 400ml Can
    </string>
    <string name="lu1802_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Movable Belt Conditioner is a combination of lubricating agents formulated to stop belt from slipping. Besides, it adds more power, eases strain on bearings and stops squealing.
        \n
        \nMr Mckenic® - Movable Belt Conditioner is widely used on canvas, leather, fabric or rubber belts which are found in automotive fans, air-conditioners, industrial and other belt driven machineries, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 400ml Can
    </string>
    <string name="lu1809_description">
        Mr McKenic®- Silicon Spray is formulated as a multi-protective spray for all metal surfaces. Besides it is also a good mould release agent. It can also be use on rubber seal* for protection and lubrication. Widely used in hospitals, workshops, paper cutting industries, mould injection industries, etc.
        \n
        \nMr Mckenic® - Silicon Spray is widely used in automotive industries, military, moulding industries, high speed rotary letterpress printing, bindery industry, food and beverage industry processing etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 400ml Can
    </string>
    <string name="lu1822_description">
        Mr McKenic - Silicon Oil is formulated as a multi-protective lubricant for all metal, plastics or rubber. Besides it is also a good mould release agent. Widely used in hospitals, workshops, paper cutting industries, mould injection industries, garment industries, etc
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 5 Liter, 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="lu1823_description">
        Mr.Mckenic Compressor Oils use premium fully synthetic base compressor oils and additives of the highest quality in order to provide outstanding performance and superior protection. These lubricants are highly resistant to cold climates and low temperatures and have exceptional thermal and oxidation stability properties, paired with a very high viscosity index. These characteristics enable a wide operating temperature range and help them perform efficiently even when exposed to elevated compressed-air temperatures.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="lu1825_1_description">
        Mr McKenic® -Gear Oil M220 is technically designed as an extreme pressure gear lubricant.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Gear Oil M220 is widely used in enclosed gear sets , spar ,helical and bevel designs, worm gears, lubrication of bearings, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="lu1825_2_description">
        Mr McKenic® -Gear Oil M320 is technically designed as an extreme pressure gear lubricant.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Gear Oil M320 is widely used in enclosed gear sets , spar ,helical and bevel designs, worm gears, lubrication of bearings, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="lu1825_description">
        Mr McKenic® -.Gear Oil M150 is technically designed as an extreme pressure gear lubricant
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Gear Oil M150 is widely used in enclosed gear sets , spar ,helical and bevel designs, worm gears, lubrication of bearings, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="lu1826_1_description">

        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="lu1826_description">
        Mr McKenic® -Hydraulic Oil M68 is technically designed to provide equipments protection under severe conditions.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Hydraulic Oil M68 is widely used gear, radial vane and axial piston pumps.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="lu1826_m46_description">
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="lu1827_chain_description">
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="lu1827_gear_description">
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="lu1835_1_description">
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="lu1835_description">
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="me1201_1_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Penetrant Oil is specially formulated with multi-functional capabilities, with the potential to assist our everyday life in limitless ways. It penetrates into stiff bolts and nuts and helps to loosen them much more effectively. It can displace moisture from electrical contact points, lubricate moving parts, protect against corrosion, remove stubborn oil stains and much more… For you to explore!
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Penetrant Oil is widely used in factories, manufacturing plants, food processing plants, schools,hospitals, camps, shopping complexes, boiler rooms, automotives, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 400ml ,5 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="me1208_description">
        Mr McKenic® – 9-in-1 Technology Oil is a multi-functional product with a wide variety of applications with its lubricating, corrosion-inhibiting, penetrating and cleaning properties. An effective solution in many situations from lubricating moving parts to maintenance of equipment, Mr McKenic® – 9-in-1 Technology Oil is an essential product in every tool box.
        \n
        \nTechnically formulated with a low surface tension, Mr McKenic® – 9-in-1 Technology Oil has the ability to penetrate deeply and quickly to break up hardened grease, rust and dirt that cause friction. This excellent penetrating action frees seized mechanisms swiftly, leaving a lubricating film that further reduces frictional resistance to smoothen motion. Hence, effectively eliminates squeaks without any sticky residues.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 250ml, 450ml, 5 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3901_1_description">
        Mr Mckenic - Scale and corrosion inhibitor is a cooling water conditioner which controls the scale, corrosion and rust formation.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic - Scale and corrosion Inhibitor is widely used in the cooling water systems, condensers, process towers, heat exchangers, boilers, water tanks, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3902_1_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Concentrated Liquid Descaler is formulated to remove rust, scale, corrosion, slime, calcium or magnesium deposits, hard water deposits, etc, that have built up on cooling towers, pipings and boilers.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Concentrated Liquid Descaler is widely used in air-conditioning systems, cooling towers, condensers, heating systems, boilers and laundry industries found in hotels, complexes, marines, industries, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3905_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Non-Fuming Descaler is formulated to remove rust, scale, corrosion, slime, calcium or magnesium deposits, hard water deposits etc, that have build up on cooling towers, pipelines and boilers.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Non- Fuming Descaler is widely used in air-conditioning systems, cooling towers, condensers, heating systems, boilers and laundry industries found in hotels, complexes, marines, industries, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3907_1_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Algae-Con is formulated to eliminated, control and prevent algae and slime growth.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Algae-Con is widely used in cooling towers, feed water systems, ponds, sewage systems, fountains, storage tanks, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3907_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Algaecide (Liquid) is formulated to eliminate, control and prevent algae and slime growth.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Algaecide (Liquid) is widely used in cooling towers, feed water systems, ponds, sewage systems, fountains, storage tanks, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3909_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Biocide is formulated to control microbiological slime, bacteria and algae
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Biocide is widely used in industrial and commercial re-circulating cooling water systems, fountains, pools, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3910_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Anti-Foam Agent is formulated as a fast acting defoamer to prevent over-flowing of foam during chemical cleaning jobs.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Anti-Foam Agent is widely used in cooling towers, boilers, detergent and shampoo industries, fountains, ponds, waste areas, chemical tanks, air-washers, sewage areas. etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3912_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Oxygen Scavenger (Powder) is a highly  active oxygen scavenger designed for the removal of dissolved oxygen from boilers and feed water.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Oxygen Scavenger (Powdered) is widely used in the boilers, found in marines, aviations, industries, automotives, hospitals, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 20 Kg Pail
    </string>
    <string name="wt3919_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Boiler Conditioner SP is formulated to prevent and reduce rust, scale, pitting, corrosion, slime, calcium or magnesium deposits, hard water deposits, in boiler systems
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Concentrated Liquid Descaler is widely used in boilers found in marine, aviation, automotive, hospital and other general industries
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3920_2_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Boiler Conditioner is formulated to prevent and reduce scale, rust, oxygen pitting, corrosion and sludge in boiler systems.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Boiler Conditioner is widely used in the boilers found in marines, aviations, industries, automotives, hospitals, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3921_1_description">
        Mr McKenic® - M2000(1) is formulated to prevent and reduce scale, rust, corrosion and sludge in generator systems.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - M2000(1) is widely used in power plants, generator systems, etc…. found in marines, aviations, industries, automotives, industries, hospitals, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3933_1_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Cooling Water Treatment -DA is formulated to eliminate, control and prevent algae and slime growth.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Cooling Water Treatment-DA is widely used in cooling towers, feed water systems, ponds, sewage systems, fountains, storage tanks, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3933_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Cooling Water Treatment -DA is formulated to eliminate, control and prevent algae and slime growth.
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Cooling Water Treatment-DA is widely used in cooling towers, feed water systems, ponds, sewage systems, fountains, storage tanks, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>
    <string name="wt3934_description">
        Mr McKenic® - Cooling Water Treatment-NT is formulated to control microbiological slime, bacteria and algae
        \n
        \nMr McKenic® - Cooling Water Treatment-NT is widely used in industrial and commercial re-circulating cooling water systems, fountains, pools, etc.
        \n
        \nAvailable Sizes: 25 Liter
    </string>



    //Services Description
    
    <string name="service_1_duct_fabrication_description">
        The fabrication process for ducts involves precisely cutting and bending sheet metal into the desired cylindrical or rectangular shapes. Damodor Engineering Department has the most up to date equipment to complete the task in hand with utmost professionalism.
    </string>
    <string name="service_2_duct_material_supply_description">
        The Damodor Engineering Department can source all the required material and manpower for the ducting job at hand. The engineering team is well trained and has good understanding of the ducting work.
    </string>
    <string name="service_3_pipeline_fabrication_description">
        Cutting, beveling, and welding piping components like pipes, tees, elbows, flanges, reducers, etc are done by the Damodor Engineering department. Piping fabrication is a highly critical activity requiring high precision and involving hundreds of components and thousands of steps.
    </string>
    <string name="service_4_all_kinds_of_insulation_supply_work_description">
        The Damodor Engineering Department has a good understanding of the market in Bangladesh. We can source any kind of insulation material for our clients. We can import materials from foreign countries as well.
    </string>
    <string name="service_5_fabrication_and_installation_works_description">
        Constructing products by combining typically standardized parts using one or more individual processes. For example, steel fabrication is the production of metal structures using a range of processes such as cutting, bending and assembling. Damodor Engineering Team consists of highly trained fabricators who are able to fabricate metals maintaining high quality.
    </string>
    <string name="service_6_all_kinds_of_pipe_supply_description">
        Damodor Engineering team is able to fabricate pipes of different materials which very high efficiency. Our team ensures the maximum heat insulation of pipes in factories and power plants.
    </string>
    <string name="service_7_hydrant_system_fabrication_and_installation_works">
        Damodor Engineering team is one of the leading fire hydrant system installer in Bangladesh. Our team has experience of over 7 years in installing fire hydrant systems and our engineers are accustomed to the procedure.
    </string>
    <string name="service_8_fabrication_and_installation_material_supply_works">
        The Damodor Engineering team has a good understanding of the Bangladeshi market and can source all kind of insulation material for their fabrication need. Our fabricators are top of the line and best in the industry. We provide a complete solution for our clients. From gathering materials to installation of the insulation using fabricated support.
    </string>
    <string name="service_9_all_kinds_of_ss_ms_gp_component_supply">
        Damodor Engineering Department can provide you all kind of SS , MS , GP components. We ensure that the supplied components are of quality and high standard. Our team is experienced and we have filtered the best suppliers from around Bangladesh.
    </string>



</resources>